HABIB SEIFZADEH

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER with more than 15 years of hands-on experience in full SDLC of enterprise applications. Expert in object-oriented principles such as SOLID and design patterns as well as architectural styles like MVC. I also have an eye for details, good communication skills, and enthusiasm for facing new challenges.



CONTACT

habibseifzadeh@gmail.com

+61 413 024 423

Moncrieff, Canberra, ACT, Australia

@habibseifzadeh

in Habib Seifzadeh

SKILLS

Programming

PHP Java

JavaScript **Python**

HTML/SCSS

Databases

MySQL Microsoft SQL

SQLite

Frameworks and Methods

Laravel VueJS/Vuex

Eloquent

Scrum

Cloud based Platforms

Amazon AWS

Issue Tracking (e.g., Azure Devops, Jira, Trello, ...)

Operating Systems

Linux

Windows

Software & Tools

PhpStorm

PHPUnit

XDebug Docker

Jenkins

Git

Languages

English (Certified NAATI interpreter)

Persian



000

CERTIFICATES

- LinkedIn top 5% of PHP programmers
- LinkedIn top 15% of object-orientation

ABOUT ME

I am Habib, a developer and software engineer who not only have extensive experience in IT industry, but also always keen to update my knowledge by using state-of-the-art technologies in the projects. I am able to deliver a wide range of products based on customers' needs, from fast-delivered Wordpress websites to high-quality ones using sophisticated frameworks and tools.

WORK HISTORY

April 2016 - Present

♀ IPCO Limited, Isfahan

Senior Software Engineer

Some developed websites: http://talayemahdi.ir, http://salamatdorin.ir, http://amanatsoft.ir

September 2005 - March 2016

Dade Varze Mabna Engineering Co.

Developer & Software Engineer

Isfahan

Some developed websites: http://dibabuilding.com.au, http://amanatit.com

EDUCATION

September 2003 - July 2006

♀ Najafabad, Isfahan

Master of Software Enginnering

September 1999 - June 2003 **♀** Najafabad, Isfahan

Bachelor of Software Enginnering

ACHIEVEMENTS, HONOURS AND AWARDS

- Treated a generic e-shop system so that it be applied to nearly every business with minimun code change (Have been sold to 5 different businesses)
- ₱ Developed REST APIs to make a VB6 legacy system to be useful again.
- Performed international projects (e.g., from Canada, Iceland and Australia)
- ▼ Led a team of researchers to do a successful piece of research for Isfahan Municipality to migrate their systems to open-source and reduce their costs
- ▼ Improved several programs' performances to give their users satisfaction
- ▼ Established continuous integration tools to reduce the deployment people

GENERAL SKILLS

Fan of new challenges **Punctual** Believe in synergy Swift learner Critical thinker Meticulous Tolerant **Good Communication Skills**

A DAY OVERVIEW

